betonmarkets.com 2008-10-24

# BetOnMarkets - The World of Financial Trading

We recognize the importance of protecting your personal and financial information.

The personal information that we obtain about you assists us in servicing your account. We know you may be concerned about what we do with this information, and with financial information about your account. The following outlines our privacy practices.

## Use of Information

The Data Protection laws and regulations place obligations on users of personal data and lay down principles for fair and lawful processing of this information. We are committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We only use your personal information to help us service your account, to improve our services to you, and to provide you with products you have requested. We do not sell your personal information to third parties, but we may provide your personal information to payment providers to facilitate transactions on your account.

Your personal information is used primarily as a way of authenticating you as the proper owner of your account and as the person to whom withdrawal payments may be made. We collect personal data relating to you directly from you when you fill in the account opening form. In the event of any doubt as to the authenticity of your account details or of any withdrawal request, the company reserves the right to request further authentication information as may be deemed appropriate under the circumstances.

The above personal data that we collect will be held by us and processed for any purpose as may be allowed by law or required by any law. We may also transfer such personal data to any company within the Regent Markets Group of companies or any of our business associates.

Please note that our website generates log files that record the IP addresses of accesses to your account. This information is gathered with the sole purpose of assisting in the unlikely event of a need to investigate accesses to your account by unauthorized users. Additionally we may verify certain of the information you supply in the account opening form, or otherwise, with third-party information providers.

Please note that you may update your personal information at any time by logging into the "Settings" section of your account. It is your responsibility to ensure that BetOnMarkets is promptly and continually informed of any change in your personal information.

## Security Statement

We are committed to making sure your personal data and transactions are secure:

  * Your password and login ID are unique and passwords are encrypted so that not even BetOnMarkets staff can read them. This is the reason why we cannot retrieve your password and have to issue you with a new one to your email address if you cannot recall it.
  * We maintain customer balances in cash or cash equivalent. We ensure that 100% of each customer's balance is available for immediate withdrawal, subject to verification.
  * All credit card details are submitted directly to the Visa/Mastercard network using the latest SSL encryption technology, in accordance with bank policies.
  * Our information security policies are based on industry best practices in access control and business continuity.
  * We use identity verification services and real-time fraud detection measures to help protect you from unauthorized access to your account. We also monitor account activity for signs of unusual activity that might indicate fraud and work with collection agencies and law-enforcement agencies to address fraud issues.

## Cookies

This website does not collect personally identifying information about you except when you specifically and knowingly provide it. There is a technology called "cookies" which can be used to provide tailored information from a website. A cookie is an element of data that a website can send to your browser, which may then store it on your system. You can set your browser to notify you when you receive a cookie, giving you the chance to decide whether to accept it. If you do not accept the cookie, then you will need to input your loginID and password again at every form required to enter into the system. You are advised to choose this option if you have concerns about the security of your personal browser or PC.

## Links

This website contains links to other websites and may contain banner or icon advertisements related to third-party websites. These websites and the advertisements thereof may submit cookies onto your web browser and as such are beyond our control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such websites. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of these websites, because their practices may differ from ours.

## Notification of Changes

Any changes in our privacy policy or security statement will be posted onto this website. In the event of material changes that directly affect the economic use of your personal information, we will request your prior authorization in writing before effecting such change on your account.

You also have the right to request from us to inform you about the personal data that we process about you and to request its correction where necessary. This request must be made in writing to us and signed by you as the data subject.

  * Privacy & Security

This website is marketed in the UK and Isle of Man by Regent Markets (IOM) Ltd., First Floor, Millennium House, Victoria Road, Douglas, IM2 4RW, Isle of Man, British Isles, licenced and regulated by the Gambling Supervision Commission in the Isle of Man, British Isles, current online gambling licence issued on 31 August 2007, and in the rest of the EU by Regent Markets (Malta) Ltd., 22 Airways House, Suite 6, Tower Road, Msida MSD1825, Malta, licenced and regulated by the Lotteries and Gaming Authority in Malta, licence no LGA/CL2/118/2000 issued on 28 May 2005.

[](http://condor1.betonmarkets.com//d//c_template.cgi?w=CR&l=GB&filecode=whatsnew#share_award_winner_2007)Best Fixed-Odds Financial Trading Provider
